Now we're able to lift the hoop up and off our body and put it back down.
Let's try combining the 2.
Take your first hand or right hand in my instance because I hoop to the left.
Take your first hand, place it on the small of your back.
When you feel that hoop hit your hand, you're going to lift up into lasso.
Now, I'm going to bring it back down using my first hand as well.
When I see that opening, I can either stick my second hand up and into it, or I can just place it down on the body.
Once again and then slowly bring it back down.
Let's do it a little bit more smoothly now.
Right hand is going to lift up.
Do 2 rotations and then the right hand will put it back down or your first hand.
Lift up, 1, 2, and back down.
Nice.
Let's try that again.
Lifting up.
1, 2, and back down.
You can really have some fun with putting the hoop down by extending that second arm through the hoop, turning slowly and then giving the hoop a whirl.
If you'd like, you can do that quick.
Up, down, up, down.
Lift ups and drop downs are a lot of fun, so play with them and make this trick your own.